dinarbanker.com 2015-05-21

# Privacy Policy - Buy and Sell Iraqi Dinar and foreign currency at Sterling Currency Group

Sterling Currency Group knows you care how your information is used, and we appreciate your trust that we will use it carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy.  
By visiting us and placing an order, you are accepting the privacy policy described below.

**1\. What Personal Information Do We Collect?**  
\- Information You Provide. We receive and store information you enter (for example, when you search for or buy a product, or when you supply information such as your address, phone number or email address). We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, improving our website, and communicating with you.  
\- Cookies. Like many websites, we use "cookies." Cookies are small programs that we transfer to your hard drive that allow us to recognize you and to provide you with a customized shopping experience. If you do not want us to use cookies, you can easily disable them by going to the toolbar of your web browser and clicking on the “help” button. Follow the instructions that will prevent the browser from accepting cookies, or set the browser to inform you when you receive a new cookie. In addition, you may visit this and other websites anonymously through the use of utilities provided by other private companies.  
\- Other Information: Every computer has an IP (Internet Protocol) address. IP addresses of computers used to visit this site are noted. In addition, we automatically collect other information such as email addresses, browser types, operating systems, and the URL addresses of sites clicked to and from this site.

**2\. How Do We Use Your Information?**  
\- Special Offers. We or our affiliates may send you special offers and notices from time to time.  
\- Law Enforcement. If we receive a lawful court order to release account or other personal information then we will comply with the law. We will also release information when necessary to protect the life, safety or property of others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**3\. How Do We Protect the Security of Your Information?**  
\- We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL)  software, which encrypts information you input.  
\- We use encryption to protect your information contained in our customer list.  
\- We use a firewall to protect against unlawful intrusion.  
\- We limit access to your information on a “need to know” basis.  
\- It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

**4\. Children**  
We do not sell products or services to children. If you are under 18, you may use this site only with involvement of a parent or guardian.

**5\. Other Websites**  
Various websites may be linked to from this site (i.e.; Better Business Bureau, CBI, etc). If you link to another site, your privacy depends on the policy of that site. We strongly urge you to check their privacy policy. Not all sites guarantee that they will not share your personally identifiable information with others. You may also wish to consult privacy guidelines such as those recommended by the Online Privacy Alliance (www.privacyalliance.org).

**6\. Contact Us**  
If you would like to learn more about our privacy policy you may contact us at (888) 346-2771. We reserve the right to modify this policy in the future.
